Copelof, Maxwell Arbitration Briefs, Exhibits, Transcripts and Decisions 5129
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New England Transportation Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division #988 & 1073., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  3/23/44. Issues: rates of pay - increase; vacations; seniority - computation; working conditions. no decision.
- New England Transportation Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division #988 & 1073., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
  2/9/44, 3/7-9/44. Issue: rates of pay. no decision.
- New York and Brooklyn Casket Co., Inc. vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, Casket Makers Union Local 3128., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  9/28/45. Issue: reinstatement - following military service. no decision.
- Pepperell Mfg. Co. vs. TWUA, Local 305., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  3/2/46. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Workers of America., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
  2/12-14/43. Issue: contracting out; past practice - managerial discretion v.; supervisors & foremen - seniority; rates of pay - adjustment; contract modification. no decision.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Workers of America., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  3/19/46. Issue: insubordination. no decision
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Workers of America., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  6/24-27/46. Issue: standards of production - incentive pay and incentive systems; rates of pay - temporary job; crew size. no decision
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Works of America., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  7/30/46 - 8/1/46. Issue: arbitrability - jurisdiction; discipline - layoff; classification of jobs - rates of pay; classification of jobs; rates of pay - incentive pay; rates of pay - equal pay for equal work; transfers - transfers of work; seniority; uni
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Works of America., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  11/8/46. Issue: contracting out - decision only.
- Plush Manufacturers of Woonsocket, R.I. vs. Industrial Trades Union of America., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  3/21/47. Issue: rates of pay - increase. no decision.
- Riverside Worsted Co., Inc. vs. Industrial Trades Union of America. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  no date. Issue: rates of pay. no decision.
- Rock Hill Printing & Finishing Co. vs. TWUA, Local 710., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  11/6/47. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment. no decision.
- Rothmund, Eugene vs. United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 11., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  12/7/49. Issue: sick leave & sick pay - refusal to grant.
- Shelby Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 117., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  1/3/45. Issue: rates of pay. no decision.
- Shelby Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 117., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  1/4-5/45. Issue: rates of pay - change in product. no decision.
- Shelby Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 117., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  3/24/48. Issue: rates of pay. no decision.
- Shelby Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 117., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Issue: holidays & holiday pay. no decision
- Submarine Signal Co. vs. UE, Local 253., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Issue: management rights - workweek. no decision.
- Submarine Signal Co. vs. UE, Local 253. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  no date. Issue: rates of pay; workweek - change; severance pay - voluntary quit; discipline - discharge; layoff; classification of jobs; layoff - seniority. no decision
- Symington - Gould Corp. vs. USW, Local 1630., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  3/10/49. Issue: seniority - return of supervisors to bargaining unit. no decision
- Taber Instrument Corp. vs. UE, Local 308., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  2/17/47. Issue: discrimination - union representatives. no decision.
- Trailways of New England, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1318., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  6/29/49. Issue: rates of pay - increase; sick leave; working conditions - protective clothing; working conditions - wash up time; rates of pay - recall.
- Trailways of New England, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employes of America, Division 1318. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  no date. Issue: overtime; vacations - eligibility; working conditions - protective clothing. no decision.
- Valley Motor Transit Co. vs. IAM, Local 1019., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  6/21-22/44. Issue: interest arbitration. no decision
- Valley Motor Transit Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street & Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  7/18/44. Issue: interest arbitration. no decision.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  9/16/48. Company's hearing memo. Issue: job classification
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  12/9/49. Transcript. Issue: rate revision - change in operations
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  9/17/48. Company's post hearing memo. Issue: rate of pay; new equipment; added duties.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  12/9/48. 12/10/48 - 1/4/49. Transcripts. Issue: wage increase - change in operations.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  6/8/48. Company's post hearing memo. Issue: rate of pay; new job; discrimination
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  6/8/48. Company's post hearing memo. Issue: rate revision.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  9/16/48. Company's post hearing memo. Issue: rate of pay - job classification.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. & United Paperworkers of America, CIO, Local 675., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  9/16/48. Company's post hearing memo. Issue: job classification
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675. CIO., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  1/4/49 & 1/5/49. Transcripts. See Box 26 FF 8.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  1/4/49 & 1/5/49. Company's post hearing memo & transcript. Issue: creation of new job.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  1/18/49. Transcript. Issue: elimination of jobs.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  2/24/49. Transcript & company's post hearing memo. Issue: promotions; classification of jobs; retroactive pay.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  2/25/49. Transcript & Company's post hearing memo. Issue: discharge - improper personal conduct - off duty misconduct.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  2/25/49. Company's post hearing memo & transcript. Issue: layoff - placement during; training & trial periods.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  5/18/49. Issue: assignment of jobs - change of location.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  6/23/49. Issue: supervisors & foremen - elimination of jobs.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  6/24/49. Transcript. Issue: remedy for improper layoff.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  11/9/49 & 11/10/49. Transcripts & company's post hearing memos. Issue: rate of pay - increase; change in operations
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  6/24/49 Transcript. Issue: rate revision; workload; reclassification.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  6/24/49. Transcript. Issue: rate revision.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 676., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  6/24/49. Transcript. Issue: call-in for overtime
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  11/10/49. Transcript. Issue: rate revision; workload
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  11/12/49. Transcript. Issue: reduction in force - lack of work
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  1/4/50. Award. Issue: creation of a new job.
- West Virginia Pulp & Paper Co. vs. UPA, Local 675., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  1/6/50. Issue: reclassification.
- Westinghouse Air Brake Co. & UE, Local 610. Transcript., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  6/27/45. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift preference - seniority
- Wickwire Spencer Steel Division & USW, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  (briefs for arbitrator - no award) - arbitration held. 11/5/48. Issue: reporting pay.
- Wilten Woolen Co. & Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers of UTWA, Local 15., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  (briefs - no award) Hearing held. 7/11/45. Issue: rates of pay: 1) increases 2) computation of overtime 3) overpayment of wages 4) overpayment of wages
- Wind Innersole & Counter Co. & F.W. Filoon Co. vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Cut Sole Local., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  10/20/41. Issue: wage increase.